After you complete your onboarding
and training videos,
you can now search and accept
available jobs for your role
and any roles under you by clicking
on the Job Board icon.
You can filter by location, radius,
community, start date, lot number, or workers,
then simply click Apply.
Select any job shown to see
the actual location on the map.
You will see estimated start and completion
dates shown for each job.
To accept a job, click on the checkbox next
to the lot number and click Register.
You will then be asked to confirm that
you want to register for that job.
After clicking Confirm, any accepted jobs
will now appear under the My Jobs icon.
You can accept jobs up to two weeks out
and view later dates.
But don't worry, the system will prevent you
from accepting jobs that will create overlapping to ensure quality work.